Now, some people think the members of the GOP caucus aren't interested in anything logical.
They just want to see the world burn, as Alfred Pennyworth put it in The Dark Knight.
But I see a method in the madness.
A week ago, Donald Trump posted a comment saying that a government shutdown, quote,
is the last chance to defund these political prosecutions against me and other patriots.
You get it?
To delay justice, Donald Trump would cut off paychecks to a couple million service members and federal workers
and furlough more than a million workers and pay them later for having not worked.
They would halt food assistance to millions of moms and kids and keep NIH and my district
from enrolling any more patients in life-and-death clinical research trials.
Trump's convinced that if we shut the government down, his four criminal prosecutions on 91 different
felony and misdemeanor charges will be defunded and delayed long enough to keep him from having
to go before a jury of his peers before the 2024 election.
And like flying monkeys on a mission for the Wicked Witch of the West, Trump's followers
in the House now carry his messages out to the world, shut down the government, shut down
the prosecutions.
But the cult master has another command for his followers, which brings us here today.
On August 27th, he posted this edict.
Either impeach the bum or fade into oblivion.
They did it to us.